[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Bob, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Bob", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Good, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "I couldn't think of a better person, really, given the events of the last month, in a sense.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "n't", "think", "of", "a", "better", "person", ",", "really", ",", "given", "the", "events", "of", "the", "last", "month", ",", "in", "a", "sense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "RP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "What do you say to those people?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "those", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, in the case of the gun situation, the only reason I addressed it was because the jumping off point was a murder-suicide involving an NFL player.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "the", "case", "of", "the", "gun", "situation", ",", "the", "only", "reason", "I", "addressed", "it", "was", "because", "the", "jumping", "off", "point", "was", "a", "murder-suicide", "involving", "an", "NFL", "player", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Yes, but see, I thought the reaction was absurd and, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "see", ",", "I", "thought", "the", "reaction", "was", "absurd", "and", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Some of it was, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Some", "of", "it", "was", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "PERSON": ["Wayne LaPierre"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Why do they stand in front of reasonable reforms?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "they", "stand", "in", "front", "of", "reasonable", "reforms", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, you see, Bob, the NRA is not the problem, as you and I know, because I've got a clip here from Wayne LaPierre.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "see", ",", "Bob", ",", "the", "NRA", "is", "not", "the", "problem", ",", "as", "you", "and", "I", "know", ",", "because", "I", "'ve", "got", "a", "clip", "here", "from", "Wayne", "LaPierre", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "And that's what happened with a 5 -year- old kid -- I'm sorry that they had to suffer a tragedy -- but what sort of parent buys a kid a usable -- not a toy gun, but a usable gun with ammunition and then walks away and the kid kills his 2 -year-old sister?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "what", "happened", "with", "a", "5", "-year-", "old", "kid", "--", "I", "'m", "sorry", "that", "they", "had", "to", "suffer", "a", "tragedy", "--", "but", "what", "sort", "of", "parent", "buys", "a", "kid", "a", "usable", "--", "not", "a", "toy", "gun", ",", "but", "a", "usable", "gun", "with", "ammunition", "and", "then", "walks", "away", "and", "the", "kid", "kills", "his", "2", "-year-old", "sister", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP$", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "But -- but let me ask a different question.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "--", "but", "let", "me", "ask", "a", "different", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Yes, you can blame irresponsible parents, but what kind of society that is part of the great superpower of the world allows a company like Crickett to be deliberately marketing and selling guns to 5-year-olds?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "can", "blame", "irresponsible", "parents", ",", "but", "what", "kind", "of", "society", "that", "is", "part", "of", "the", "great", "superpower", "of", "the", "world", "allows", "a", "company", "like", "Crickett", "to", "be", "deliberately", "marketing", "and", "selling", "guns", "to", "5-year-olds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "And let's also understand, the NRA is a gun lobby, like any other lobbying organization --", "answer_tokens": ["And", "let", "'s", "also", "understand", ",", "the", "NRA", "is", "a", "gun", "lobby", ",", "like", "any", "other", "lobbying", "organization", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "LOCATION": ["Houston"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Where is the outrage?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "the", "outrage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Well, look, the NRA convention just concluded in Houston.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "the", "NRA", "convention", "just", "concluded", "in", "Houston", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Care to respond, Bob?", "question_tokens": ["Care", "to", "respond", ",", "Bob", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "I think that puts it mildly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "puts", "it", "mildly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Gerald?", "question_tokens": ["Gerald", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "What made you desire to become a sports broadcaster in the first place, and since becoming one of the best, what is your take on how the profession has changed since your early days at NBC in the 1970s?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "desire", "to", "become", "a", "sports", "broadcaster", "in", "the", "first", "place", ",", "and", "since", "becoming", "one", "of", "the", "best", ",", "what", "is", "your", "take", "on", "how", "the", "profession", "has", "changed", "since", "your", "early", "days", "at", "NBC", "in", "the", "1970s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I wanted to be a sports announcer because I -- I loved sports as a kid and I was also enchanted by the voices of sport.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "wanted", "to", "be", "a", "sports", "announcer", "because", "I", "--", "I", "loved", "sports", "as", "a", "kid", "and", "I", "was", "also", "enchanted", "by", "the", "voices", "of", "sport", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1970s"], "ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "But what was the moment for you when the blinkers maybe came off and you realized he is a cheat?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "was", "the", "moment", "for", "you", "when", "the", "blinkers", "maybe", "came", "off", "and", "you", "realized", "he", "is", "a", "cheat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, I think the evidence was accumulating year after year and there was so much smoke, you figure there had to be fire.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "evidence", "was", "accumulating", "year", "after", "year", "and", "there", "was", "so", "much", "smoke", ",", "you", "figure", "there", "had", "to", "be", "fire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "And he was a good liar, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "was", "a", "good", "liar", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "He was a very good liar, because he was intelligent and he had a series of facts, or what he purported to be facts, rather than evasions, and he did have the one thing going for him, that he had been tested repeatedly in and out of competition and never failed a drug test.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "a", "very", "good", "liar", ",", "because", "he", "was", "intelligent", "and", "he", "had", "a", "series", "of", "facts", ",", "or", "what", "he", "purported", "to", "be", "facts", ",", "rather", "than", "evasions", ",", "and", "he", "did", "have", "the", "one", "thing", "going", "for", "him", ",", "that", "he", "had", "been", "tested", "repeatedly", "in", "and", "out", "of", "competition", "and", "never", "failed", "a", "drug", "test", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "He was bigger, though, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "bigger", ",", "though", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "He looked you, Bob Costas, in the eye, one of the most respected men, yourself, in American sport, and just sold you a complete pack of lies?", "question_tokens": ["He", "looked", "you", ",", "Bob", "Costas", ",", "in", "the", "eye", ",", "one", "of", "the", "most", "respected", "men", ",", "yourself", ",", "in", "American", "sport", ",", "and", "just", "sold", "you", "a", "complete", "pack", "of", "lies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "You know, I didn't take it personally.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "take", "it", "personally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Costas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "ORGAN: Did he ever apologize to you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "he", "ever", "apologize", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Roll that tape, will you?", "question_tokens": ["Roll", "that", "tape", ",", "will", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "(INAUDIBLE) is hot.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "is", "hot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Would you let me finish?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "let", "me", "finish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Bob, what were you thinking when that was all going on?", "question_tokens": ["Bob", ",", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "when", "that", "was", "all", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Well, here was the deal.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "was", "the", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "It's like some anachronistic old gentleman's club, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", "some", "anachronistic", "old", "gentleman", "'s", "club", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Well, a couple of things about this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "couple", "of", "things", "about", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Daniel?", "question_tokens": ["Daniel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "This is an unbelievable interview.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "an", "unbelievable", "interview", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "What is the single best sports moment you have ever seen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "single", "best", "sports", "moment", "you", "have", "ever", "seen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NNS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I can't narrow it to one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "narrow", "it", "to", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBA"], "PERSON": ["Jim Brown"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Who is the greatest sportsman you have ever seen in any sport, for whatever reason?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "greatest", "sportsman", "you", "have", "ever", "seen", "in", "any", "sport", ",", "for", "whatever", "reason", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Perhaps the greatest all around athlete would be Jim Brown, the great American football player, who also could have been the greatest lacrosse player who ever lived, undoubtedly could have played basketball in the NBA.", "answer_tokens": ["Perhaps", "the", "greatest", "all", "around", "athlete", "would", "be", "Jim", "Brown", ",", "the", "great", "American", "football", "player", ",", "who", "also", "could", "have", "been", "the", "greatest", "lacrosse", "player", "who", "ever", "lived", ",", "undoubtedly", "could", "have", "played", "basketball", "in", "the", "NBA", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "It is about winning, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "about", "winning", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "I think a lot of people are able to separate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "are", "able", "to", "separate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "There are the cheats and the non-cheats, aren't there?", "question_tokens": ["There", "are", "the", "cheats", "and", "the", "non-cheats", ",", "are", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Well, there's some validity in that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "some", "validity", "in", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1988"], "PERSON": ["Ted Williams"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "What would you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Well, I interviewed Ted Williams, who some people think is the greatest hitter of all time, in 1988, at a time when he had not done an interview, radio or television, at all, in 15, 16 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "interviewed", "Ted", "Williams", ",", "who", "some", "people", "think", "is", "the", "greatest", "hitter", "of", "all", "time", ",", "in", "1988", ",", "at", "a", "time", "when", "he", "had", "not", "done", "an", "interview", ",", "radio", "or", "television", ",", "at", "all", ",", "in", "15", ",", "16", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "In retrospect, was that true?", "question_tokens": ["In", "retrospect", ",", "was", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Because you hadn't been the ball player you felt you should have been?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "had", "n't", "been", "the", "ball", "player", "you", "felt", "you", "should", "have", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Or the daddy.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "the", "daddy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Completely innocent and falsely accused in every aspect?", "question_tokens": ["Completely", "innocent", "and", "falsely", "accused", "in", "every", "aspect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, I could say that, you know, I have done some of those things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "could", "say", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "have", "done", "some", "of", "those", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Is there one?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "I could ask the same question of you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "ask", "the", "same", "question", "of", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Do you believe you finally got to the right place for you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "you", "finally", "got", "to", "the", "right", "place", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "I'm in a very, very good place.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "in", "a", "very", ",", "very", "good", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Clark"], "LOCATION": ["Syracuse"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "And will you share it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "will", "you", "share", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "You know, Dick Clark went to Syracuse as I did.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Dick", "Clark", "went", "to", "Syracuse", "as", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "So why change it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "change", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Let's go to a quick quiz.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "go", "to", "a", "quick", "quiz", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Do you know what a -- if I said I was bowling you a googly, and I had two silly mid ones and a fine leg, would you know what the hell I'm talking about?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "a", "--", "if", "I", "said", "I", "was", "bowling", "you", "a", "googly", ",", "and", "I", "had", "two", "silly", "mid", "ones", "and", "a", "fine", "leg", ",", "would", "you", "know", "what", "the", "hell", "I", "'m", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "I would say the police probably brought you home in the middle of the night.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "the", "police", "probably", "brought", "you", "home", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "the", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "I'm sure it doesn't involve him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sure", "it", "does", "n't", "involve", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Do you get that with fries at McDonald's?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "that", "with", "fries", "at", "McDonald", "'s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "That's an McRib.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "an", "McRib", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["McDonald's"]}}]